

Preferred name / Haillie

light.blue.389@gmail.com 778-798-2546 www.github.com/HaesunJo www.linkedin.com/in/hailliejo haesunjo.github.io/haillie\_portfolio/

#### Skills

Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, JAVA,

TypeScript, jQuery

Version management

Git, GitHub

os

Mac, Window

Frameworks

React, ReactNative, Vue.js, Bootstrap, Expo Go, SpringBoots, Express

Server technologies

Node.js, Apache, MAMP

Others

Figma, in Vision, Adobe Photoshop / Illustration

Tools

Android Studio, Workbench, Firebase

Database

MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB

## Projects

Portfolio page / Web app - SPA / HTML, CSS, Vanilla Javacsript, Git, Git page

+ Link | https://haesunjo.github.io/haillie\_portfolio/

2021 10 - 2022 03

The portfolio website was developed with HTML, CSS, and vanilla JavaScript and deployed by the git page for learning purposes. It has two theme colors that light mode and dark mode when you click a switch. There is a form that you can contact via email linked to my Gmail account. During building this web page I've learnt lots of stuff about the skills I used such as classList property that helps the code works clean and efficiently.

Weather App / Mobile app - SPA / Personal Project / React Native, Expo Go

+ Demo link | https://expo.dev/@haillie/WeatherApp

The weather forecast App has the weather API and catches the user's location with longitude and latitude. Used hooks 'useState' for storing days, city, and location service status, also used hooks useEffect' when it requests permission to get the user's location from the user. This app was developed using React Native and Expo Go.

Check your list / Mobile app - SPA / Personal Project / Reac tNative, Expo Go

+ Demo link | https://expo.dev/@haillie/projects/CheckYourList

2022.01 - 2022.02

2022.01 - 2022.02

Developed a To-Do-List app. In this project, Async is used for storing, loading, editing and so on, the data that the user added. The data will be saved in JSON format and parsed the data as string values. Bring the data to the screen such as task, check box if the user completes the task. This app was developed using React Native and Expo Go.

Messenger / Web app - SPA / Personal Project / React, Firebase, Chat Engin

+ Demo link | https://talk-and-chat-mastery.netlify.app/

2022.01 - 2022.02

This is a messenger web app based on firebase so users can log in with Google or Facebook accounts. When the user clicks either Google or Facebook user will be redirected to what the user chooses. Learned Chat engine API, Firebase and React.js as the primary frontend framework.

Fitness at Home / Web app / School project / Vue.js, Springboot, Bootstrap 2.21.2(Latest for vue.js)

2021.03 - Curren

Programmed one of the main services in this project is a 'Review board' that has CRUD functions which I played a role. Also, managed and assigned a task for each member and documentation of what each team member had worked on. This web app was developed using Vue.js with Bootstrap as the primary frontend framework, and Sprinboot as the primary backend framework.

Blurry Spoiler / Web app - SPA / Project for learning purpose / Eta framwork, Vailla Javascript, Bootstrap 5 2022.01 - Current Project for learning purpose with another friend. Playing a key role in developing in front-end development and UX/UI design. We are expecting to deploy and launch the service in July.

### Education

#### Douglas College / Diploma

May 2019 - December 2021, New Westminster, BC

+ Computing Studies & Information Systems

### Korea Polytechnic I / Associate Degree

March 2013 -February 2015, Seoul, Korea

+ Dept. of Industrial Design

## Experience

# BNB Studio / Web Designer / Full-time

December 2017 - May 2018, Seoul, Korea

+ Maintain and redesign an official company website, also design for products detail/instruction pages

### Soodam Studio / UX/UI Designer / Full-time

August 2015 - December 2016, Seoul, Korea

+ UX/UI design for AR guide book application, work with Hyundai, KIA. Specially, leade UX/UI designer in Hyundai project

#### Eco-feel / Junior Designer / Full-time

December 2014 - May 2015, Seoul, Korea

+ Make light installed mockup images as a bird's eye view and UX/UI design for light controller software, work with Korea Institue of Lighting & ICT